Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 14, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Symbol of Security for Civil Service Clerical Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Story of a Humble Petition, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Union of Post Office Workers
  - Item 5: Wages, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Clarence H. Northcott
  - Item 6: 1946 The National Federation of Professional Workers: Some Current Activities, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: 1920-1945 The National Federation of ProfessionalIs and Does, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: What Equity is Doing: Seventeenth Annual Report of the Council, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: British Actors Equity Association
    Notes: serial/annual
  - Item 9: A Charter for Engineering and Shipbuilding Clerks, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Clerical and Administrative Workers' Union
  - Item 10: The First National Agreement, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Agreement with the British Electricity AuthorityFuture Agreement, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: So you're feeling pretty strange, said the branch secretary, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: A Guide to Typists and Shorthand Typists in the Civil Service, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Civil Service Clerical Association
  - Item 14: Introducing the Union, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Hey! Half a minute, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: When Bernard Shaw Was a Clerk, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Introducing Equity, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Your Branch: How to Start It and How to Run It, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Temporary Clerks, men and women, for your protectionprotect them, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Whitley Bulletin (several articles - April 1948), Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Civil Service National Whitley Council
  - Item 21: Male Telephonists: The U.P.W. can truly say - I can Help You, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Men are Born Free, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Lloyds Bank
  - Item 23: The Year Book of the National Union of Bank Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Thirtieth Annual Delegate Meeting: Agenda, ReportsProceedings, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Progress Report by the Deputy General Secretary, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: The Case for a National Union in Banking, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: The U.P.W. General Secretary Says: This is Your Union, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Productivity: Report of a ConferenceExecutive Committees, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Report and Financial Statement for 1948, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Service for Management, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: British Institute of Management
  - Item 31: The Clerk (several articles - July/August 1948), Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Sixty Years of the National Union of General and Municipal Workers: 1889-1949, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: National Union of General and Municipal Workers
  - Item 33: The Iron and Steel Trades in 1949: Special Review, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Author: Wiliam Jacks and Company
- Box: 14, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Your Job and Your Union, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: BACIE, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constitution, Rules and Regulations, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Transport and General Workers Union: Members Handbook, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Report of the Liberal Trade Union Commission, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Liberal Party (Great Britain). Liberal Trade Union Commission
  - Item 6: Post Office Engineering Union: Rules, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The Supervisor and the Specialists: Report of an Inquiry, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Institute of Industrial Supervisors
  - Item 8: The Workers' Educational Trade Union: Administration Finance and Structure, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Workers' Educational Trade Union Committee
  - Item 9: Trade Unionism and the New Social Order, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Roper
  - Item 10: Trade Unions Today - [Planning - vol. XV, no. 286], 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Political & Economic Planning
  - Item 11: A Short History of the Liverpool Trades Council, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: William Hamling
  - Item 12: British Trade Unions, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Production: The Bridge to Socialism, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Trade Unions in Britain - [British Information Services - Dec. 1949], Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Box: 14, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: British Trade Unions, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Defend Democracy: Communist Activities Examined, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Defend Democracy: Communist Activities Examined, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: A Common Loyalty - The Bridge to Unity, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Author: James Larkin
    Notes: Presidential address to 55th Annual meeting
  - Item 5: Education and Training in the Steel Industry: Second Training Conference, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Author: Conference on Training in the Steel Industry
  - Item 6: Trade Unions in Britain - [British Information Services - Dec. 1949], Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The T.U.C. and the W.F.T.U.: A Statement of PolicyOctober 1948, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The T.U.C. and the W.F.T.U.: A Statement of PolicyOctober 1948, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Trade Union Charts, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Industrial Democracy: Its Development and Significance to the Individual, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Author: Harold Clay
  - Item 11: Miners' Welfare 1949 --Second Annual Report of the National Miners' Welfare Joint Council, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Author: National Miners' Welfare Joint Council
  - Item 12: Report of a Court of Inquiry into a disputeColliery Winding Enginemen, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Author: National Union of Colliery Winding Enginemen; Great Britain. National Coal Board
  - Item 13: The Interim Index of Industrial Production, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: What the TUC is Doing: An Informal Accountsince September 1947, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: What the TUC is Doing: An Informal Accountsince September 1948, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Trade Unionism and the New Social Order, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Box: 14, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Ghanian Labor Legislation Since Independence, 1961; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Rates of Pay - Ghana Manufacturers' Group, 1964; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Constitution, Rules and Regulations, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Author: National Joint Council for the Building Industry
  - Item 4: Handbook of National Agreements, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Author: Confederation of Shipbuilding and Engineering Unions
  - Item 5: Productivity Report, 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Pottery Industry: Wages Structure, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Author: British Pottery Manufacturers' Federation; National Society of Pottery Workers
  - Item 7: What is the Transport T.U.I.?, 1949; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Author: Transport, Port and Fishery Workers Trade Unions International
  - Item 8: The Short Road to Industrial Cooperation: [BACIE], 1948; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Author: British Association for Commercial and Industrial Education
- Box: 14, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and Productivity: The ReportUnited States of America, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Notes: 4th copy/dupl.
  - Item 2: Letter From England, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Author: Molly Panter- Downes
    Notes: archival copy
  - Item 3: Report on Activities for the Period from 1st April till 31st December 1950, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Author: Trade Union OrganizationInternational Confederation of Free Trade Unions
  - Item 4: Trade Unions and Productivity: The Report and recommendations of a team of British trade union officials who investigated the role of unions in increasing productivity in the United States of America, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Song Sheet: Labour Anthems, Traditional Songs andFavourites, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Joint Consultation and Responsibility in Modern Industry, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Author: Joseph I. Roper
  - Item 7: Individual and Professional Membership (Provisional Handbook), 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Author: Institute of Industrial Administration (Great Britain)
  - Item 8: The Story of the Engineers, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: At the Root of it All, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Author: Great Britain. National Coal Board
- Box: 14, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Future of the Unions, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Acton Society Trust
  - Item 2: The Just Society: A Re-affirmation of Faith in Socialism, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Problem of Full Employment, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part VI Industrialof Industry, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Ernest Bevin
  - Item 5: British Labour as Government and as Opposition, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Harry Wellington Laidler
  - Item 6: European Unity: A Statement by the NationalBritish Labour Party, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Labour and the new society: a statement of the policy and principles of British democratic socialism, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Labour Party (Great Britain) National Executive Committee
  - Item 8: Monopoly, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Our First Duty - Peace: A Statement of Policy on the Problems of Today, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Quarterly Meeting, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Staff Management, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: F.W. Lawe
  - Item 12: The British Health Service, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Julius Manson
  - Item 13: Education & Training in Office & Factory: Some Bournville Schemes, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: Cadbury Brothers
- Box: 14, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Tavistock Institute of Human Relations: development and work, 1946-1950, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: Tavistock Institute of Human Relations
  - Item 2: Arbitration, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: J.R.W. Alexander
    Notes: article - reprinted from "The Secretary"
  - Item 3: Report and speeches of the British delegation, formed jointly by the British Employers' Confederation and the Federation of British Industries, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: International Conference of Manufacturers
  - Item 4: Full Employment Objectives in relation to.European Cooperation, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: Council of Europe. Secretariat
  - Item 5: Merit Rating: A Practical Guide, 1954; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Miners' Welfare 1950: Third Annual Report of the National Miners' Welfare Joint Council, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Ministry of Labour and National Service, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: Ministry of Labour and National Service
    Notes: publication list
  - Item 8: Nationalisation and the Professions, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: The Coal Miner, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: Andrew Bryan
  - Item 10: Wage Incentive Schemes, 1950; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: What the T.U.C. is Doing: An Informal.in September 1950, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: What the T.U.C. is Doing: An Informal.in September 1950, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Box: 14, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: National Joint Council for the Building Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Notes: for official use'
  - Item 2: Works Committee Members' Handbook: A manual for all representatives, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Industrial Society
  - Item 3: Jubilee Addresses on Adult Education 1953, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Workers' Educaitonal Association
  - Item 4: Why Have Hobart House?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Street, Arthur
    Notes: excerpt transcript from an address by the late Sir Arthur Street
  - Item 5: Adult Education in the United Kingdom: A Directory of Organisations, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: National Institutte of Adult Education (England and Wales)
  - Item 6: National Union of Manufacturers: Constitution and Aims, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: National Union of Manufacturers
  - Item 7: Some Problems of a Factory: An Analysis of Industrial Institutions, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Wilfred Brown
  - Item 8: Some Problems of a Factory: An Analysis of Industrial Institutions, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Some Problems of a Factory: An Analysis of Industrial Institutions, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: The Workers' Educational Association 1946-1952: A Review, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: What is the Colombo Plan?, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Guy Wint
  - Item 12: A Career for Life, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Lever Brothers Port Sunlight Limited
  - Item 13: Leadership in the Factory, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: John Munro Fraser
- Box: 14, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: National Joint Council for the Building Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Fifty Million Unemployed, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Author: Michael Dunlop Young
  - Item 3: Wages Productivity and Training, with specialChemical Industry, 1951; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Author: Bob Edwards
  - Item 4: Guide to the Scheme of Directed Practical Training, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Steel Works Engine Drivers &c. (Broken Hill Proprietary Company Ltd.), 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part III The Union at Work, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The Workers' Educational Association 1946-1952: A Review, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: 1st Annual Report of the Coal Industry Social Welfare Organisation, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Author: Coal Industry Social Welfare Organisation
    Notes: annual - serial
  - Item 9: 2nd Annual Report of the Coal Industry Social Welfare Organisation, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Box: 14, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What the T.U.C. is Doing: An Informal AccountUnion Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: A Home of Their Own: A Knotty Problem for John and Mary, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Challenge to Britain: A Programme of Action for theGovernment, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Author: Labour Party (Great Britain). Executive Committee
  - Item 4: Conciliation and Arbitration in Industrial Disputes, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Author: John Russel Willis Alexander
  - Item 5: Development of Educational Services for Trade Unionists, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Legal Aspects of Compulsory Arbitration in Great Britain, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Notes: article reprinted from Cornell Law Quarterly, vol. XXXVII, no. 3, Spring 1952
  - Item 7: Stop!, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Notes: poster/broadside
  - Item 8: The Apple's Alright, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Trade Union Wage Policy in Postwar Britain, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Author: Jean T. McKelvey
  - Item 10: Trade Union Wage Policy in Postwar Britain, 1952; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: 2nd Annual Report of the Coal Industry Social Welfare Organisation, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: WEA Retrospect 1903-1953: A RecordEducational Association, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Box: 14, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Notes on Reading - Part III, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Notes on Reading - Part II, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part I - The Background of the Union, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part I - The Background of the Union, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part V VoluntaryFixing Bodies, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part II - StructureMembership, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part II - StructureMembership, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part III The Union at Work, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part IV ProblemsEmployment, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part IV ProblemsEmployment, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part VI - Industrial Legislation, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part VI - Notes on Reading, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part VI Industrial Legislation, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Talking Points: An American Slump?, 1954; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Talking Points: Policy in the Colonies, 1954; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Challenge to Britain: A Programme of Action for theGovernment, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: ABC of the T.U.C., 1954; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Two Centuries of Trade Unionism, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part IV ProblemsEmployment, 1953; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part II - Notes on Reading, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Box: 15, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part III The Union at Work, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Union Education Scheme - Annual Reportand Grants, 1953, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Union Scholarships in 1954, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Union Summer Schools, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Bowen-Mallon Travelling Bursaries, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Workers' Educational Association in co-operation with th eWorkers' Travel Association
  - Item 6: Courses for Foremen and Supervisors, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Polytechnic. Dept. of Management Studies
    Notes: course catalog
  - Item 7: Education Department - Study Course on 'The Union, Its Work & Problems': Loan of Books, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Home Study Course on the Union's Work and Structure, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: How Do the Communists Work?, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Victor Feather
  - Item 10: London Labour and Colonial Freedom: Two Centuries of Struggle, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: Communist Party of Great Britain. London District Committee
  - Item 11: Memorandum on the Purpose, PracticeUnion's Education Scheme, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: One-Week Training Course for Branch OfficersMay & June, 1954, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: application for taking a course
  - Item 13: Scholarships for London School of EconomicsColeg Harlech, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Study Course on the Union...Certificate Questions, Third Attempt, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Study Course on the UnionCertificate Questions, First Attempt, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Study Course on the UnionCertificate Questions, Second Attempt, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Summer School Scholarships 1954, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: The Closed Shop Controversy in Postwar Britain, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: reprint from Industrial and Labor Relations Review
  - Item 19: The Social Skills of Management, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: The Trade Unionist in Britain, 1952; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: The Union, Its Work and Problems, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: The Union, Its Work and Problems: Part I - The Background of the Union, 1953; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Workers' Committee: An Outline of its Principles and Structure, 1918; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: The Sheffield Workers' Committee
  - Item 2: Jubilee Addresses on Adult Education 1953, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 34th Annual Report for the year ended 31st March 1954, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: ABC of the T.U.C., 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Careers with the National Coal Board, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Dunlop Gateways: Fort Dunlop Engineering Apprenticeship Scheme, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Dunlop Rubber Company
  - Item 7: Recommendations and StatutorySafety and Welfare in Foundries, 1954; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Author: Amalgamted Union of Foundry Workers
- Box: 15, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: To Stevedores, Dockers, Coal HeaversWarning to Dockers, 1923; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: Amalgamated Marine Workers' Union
  - Item 2: Trade Union Education, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: What the T.U.C. is Doing, 1956; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: What the T.U.C. is Doing: Trades Union Congress 1955, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: What the T.U.C. is Doing: Trades Union Congress 1955, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Annual Conference, Folkestone May 1955: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: Chartered Institute of Secretaries
  - Item 7: Initial Report of the Survey Team in adult workers' education for the United States Educational Commission in the United Kingdom, 1956; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: United States Educational Commission in the United Kingdom
  - Item 8: Labor Relations in British Metalworking, 1955; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Author: Milton Derber